{
    "id": "40dfae507829429e81da1e8535af5a52",
    "title": "Common Phrasal Verbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I am going to ask her ………………. to dinner tonight.",
            "description": "To ask somebody out is to invite them on a date.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I won’t be able to get out before you back …………….. your car.",
            "description": "To back up a car is to reverse it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My family didn’t back me ………………… over my decision to quit my job.",
            "description": "To back somebody up is to support them.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car blew ……………… after it crashed into the tree.",
            "description": "To blow up is to explode.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you blow this balloon ……………..?",
            "description": "To blow up a balloon is to inflate it.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The car broke ...................... in the storm.",
            "description": "When things break down they stop functioning.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman broke …………………. when she learned that she had cancer.",
            "description": "To break down is to cry.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you find the task difficult, break it …………….. into smaller parts.",
            "description": "To break something down is to divide it into smaller parts.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The thieves broke ……………… through the back door.",
            "description": "To break in is to enter a building forcibly.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie has called ……………. her wedding.",
            "description": "To call off wedding is to cancel it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I desperately need someone to cheer me ……………..",
            "description": "To cheer somebody up is to make them happy.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I came ……………… these old letters while organizing the closet.",
            "description": "To come across something is to find it by chance. ",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "through",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}